Good Morning
Good morning.
I'm a little ahead of you.
Letter.
A letter?
What?
What? What?
What's what?
Dear letter.
Oh!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
I know this is sudden, but...
Do you like baseball?
Oh!
Samurai Japan won the WBC.
I'm going to appear at a certain event.
I will be appearing at a certain event.
Uhhh...
What are you going to say?
Baseball?
The event in which you will all perform is
Saturday, July 15th
Yokohama Stadium on Saturday, July 15.
Yokohama DNA Bay Stars event
Blue Light Series
2023 Summer!
Yay!
Yes? Wait.
What?
For all of you...
The pre-game ceremonial pitch.
I mean, test pitch.In other words, a test pitch.
Yay!
After the game.
You can have a live performance
Congratulations.
That's great.
That's amazing.
He's going to throw 12 pitches.
Really?
It's definitely not a death sentence.
We'll work out the details of this now.
Strikes?
We get to decide?
You want to decide?
What?
First, the ceremonial pitch, the death penalty.
The three of us will go for strikes and strike out.
By three?
Strikes.
I'd like to announce the members of the team.
Oh!
Nakamura
I, Kani, from Kanagawa Prefecture, here!
Sakura Momochan!
I'm really happy!
I'd like to shoulder.
Yes, and the other one is
What a second grader!
A second grader!
Yes, that's right.
I've already made a lottery to decide the third person.
to decide who the third person will be.
And here's more.
I'd like to add one line to the lottery for each person
I'd like to add a line to the lottery for each person to decide the third person.I'd like to add to it and decide.
Wow.
Today.
I guess this one goes first?
Yes, go ahead.
Okay, one more heart here.
Oh!
It's a big heart.
A big heart.
Yes, sir.
Okay, from here.
I'd like to follow the lottery.
Yes!
First of all, I'd like to show you the result of the lottery.
Well, I mean, the result...
I'd like to show you where we'll end up.
I'd like to give you the result.
Let's do it, let's do it...
Oh!
Who's there?
Uh, I don't know. I don't know.
So, we'll just follow the trail.
Let's follow it.
Okay, here we go.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Climb? Climb?
Oh, there you are.
Oh!
Ooh.
You want to climb?
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
Yeah!
Yay!Yay!
Yay!
The third head of the family has been decided to be Shiori Nagata.
Yes! The Yushiki will be directed by Mamma Sakurai, Shiori-chan Nagata, and myself, Kari-san and Moemiko.
Please do so.
And there is one more thing to decide,
We have decided on the name of the uniform and the shape of the phone.
Yay!
Now that we have decided on the name and smart phone, we will stop Yuu-shiki.
I've also decided on Invelo 2 in eco-friendly.
What's that? I'm Aimi.
I can't really give you a name, and your birthday's in four digits.
Four digits are fine.
Next, Tanaka-san.
I'm a little scared.
I just need a minute.
I'm going to keep the name.
But there's also July 17th, so I'm thinking 717.
It's a 7 in my name.
It's a 7, and it's a lucky 7, so...
We'll see which way it goes on the show.
Oh, that's okay.
If everyone knows...
It's nice. It brings out everyone's personality.
We've decided on numbers and names.
Let's all do our best to make the day a lot of fun!
Congratulations!
That's all for now.
This is Lovelight Albie!
So, a few days later, I'll be at Yokohama Stadium, home of the BayStars, for the event.
I was at Yokohama Stadium, home of the Bay Stars
at Yokohama Stadium, home of the BayStars!
Hello everyone!
I'm Rumi Natoika!This is Natoika Rumi.
I'm Rumi Natoika.
Well, well, well.
I'm here today at Yokohama Stadium.
I'm here.
So let's get right to it.
Let's see what we're going to do today.
I'll ask you to do it.
This time, I'm going to make a video about the BayStars.
Let's make a video where you can learn more about the BayStars!
Yay!
On Saturday, July 15, I will be performing at an event hosted by the Yokohama DNA
I'll be performing at an event hosted by the Yokohama DNA BayStars on Saturday, July 15.
Natoika Rumi
So this time, the Noimee members will be
of watching baseball games at Hamasta
I'll be taking pictures of a project that will help you
to learn more about how to enjoy watching a baseball game at Hamasta.
Yes, that's right, this time we're going to take a picture of
I'm going to introduce you to the BayStars
who is well known as a BayStars player.
I'm going to ask him to tell us a lot about the Bay Stars.
I'm going to ask him to tell us about the Bay Stars.
Yes, sir.
Well then, let's begin.
Hi, I'm Shoko Takeyoki from Idolove.
Wow!
Shoko-san.
So Shoko-san is here.
Thank you very much.
I'm so excited to be here.
That's great.
These are Shoko-san's personal belongings.
Yes, personal towels and uniforms.Yes, personal towels, uniforms, and
And a cheering bat.
Oh, my God.
So cute!
Yes, that's right.
Today, Shoko is going to show us how to enjoy Hamas
I'll show you how to enjoy Hamas
Yes, I'm Shoko!
Yes, this time
We've prepared a variety of food and goods for you to enjoy in the room where you will watch the games.
Gourmet foods and goods have been prepared in the rooms where we will watch the games.
Let's head to your room right away!
Yay!
And so
All the members are heading to the room where they will watch the game.
Here's a surprise for the five of us who didn't know anything about it.
BayStars gave us a nice surprise!
Thank you very much!
Wait!
What?
Oh, my God!
Wait!
This is the one we all decided on, right?
That's what the numbers say.
I'm so happy!
Is this the one where we decide by our faces?
Yes, this time.
I'll prepare it for you this time.
Thank you very much.
This time, we have a digital fan
Mr. Takeuchi is here.
I will prepare it for you.We will be happy to match it for you.
Thank you very much.
Surprise!
May I spread it out?
Please, come.
So cute!
Do you know where the number comes from?
Mube 48 cm.
I was very careful.
My name is Saya Tabizaki.
I'm glad to hear it!
I also took two letters and my name.
That's nice
I'll show off my name.
What about Nacchan?
Nothing happened.
It's Natsume's birthday.
I'm a star.
I'm so happy.
I didn't think I'd have one either.
I'm so happy thank you
We all changed clothes together
It looks so good on you
I'm so happy
The same printed uniform as the players
All kinds of things!
Choco taught us how to wear them.
He told me how to wear it like this.
I tried to arrange it.
I'd like to get down to business now.
But before that, I'd like to meet the director of Spacetars
and Daisuke Miura, the director of the Spacetars.
Such a precious feeling!
I'm too happy!
I'm the most excited.
Today, tooToday.
you look so happy!
I would like to go and greet him as soon as possible
to meet Director Miura before the game.
I'm waiting for the director.
Good afternoon.
Good morning.
Please allow me to greet you.
I'll be appearing at the event on July 15th.
I'm Sachimi Noda.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm not going to be at the event.
I have always loved the Space Stars.
Even when I was a player.
When I was a player, I came from the people of Kalae.
I've been collaborating on a series of articles for Basestar, and I'm Hideo Tachio from Equal Round.
I'm Hideo Tachio from Equal Round.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Come to the event with everyone and
Enjoy the live music and the big massage!
Thank you very much.
for making our uniforms this time.
Thank you so much!
What's the number?
The number is in Spanish.
Suzutaka Kinoshita, to match the name Suzutaka
I am
Makoto Kitahashi.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
All the members were able to greet Director Miura without incident.
Now it's time to move on!
Presented by Mr. Shoko
Introduction of recommended cheering goods and rescue gourmet foods
First of all, we will start with the
which are indispensable for cheering.From enlivening goods indispensable for cheering
I'd like to introduce you to our most popular cheering goods.
Here it is!
Wow!
So cute!
Thank you very much!
First of all, this one...
It's called a "bay punch.
You can put your hand in here and punch it.
You can do this during the game or something.
You can do this even during the game.
It's like an event project.
If you do this, you'll be overtaken.
If you do this, they'll pull you out.
For the camera.
Very much so.
I want to see it.
I want to see.
Come on, come on.
These are the names of the players.
That's right.
Sevander.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
This is...
It's like iconoclastic.
If it means something, it's a diamond.
Iconoi joyhus.
I'm sure it's...
Joy, you're a wolf.
That's nice.
I'm sure.
Looks
Pee-chan.
Pee-wee.
Now there's something you'll never get out of that statement.There's one thing you're never going to get out of what you just said.
I know.
I'm thinking now.
This is Starman.
Starman.
It's a girl. Her name is Kirara.
She looks like her.
I want to use it on Kirara.
You know, during the games.
She dances with the cheerleaders.
She's really tall.
Big.
I can use it.
That's ...
why?
And it's back.
When you click on it...
It's like it glows.
I can't hit it right now.
It glows.
That's amazing.
Like at a night game.
Like, fans...
Like, they're waving this at us.
It's like I'm taking the place of a pervert.
Big.
Beautiful.
Make sure you're in front of it too.
I hope you enjoy it.
much with this one.
I hope you all get it!
And the catsuit.
It's so cute.
I want you to try it on.
Here.
We have five of them.We have five.
I have five.
How many?
It's so soft to the touch.
It's so soft.
It's soft.
There you go.
So...
It's like putting it in a cake.
Okay, let's get started.
I'd like to put it on.
Se
Seyla's neck cover.
Cute!
So cute!
Amazing.
And in here, towels, fireproof grasshoppers, and more.
You've had a good preview of the goods!
Next, the gourmet food you've been waiting for!
Curry, fried chicken, etc.
but the best of all
The most recommended one among them is
Yes, and...
One of the joys of attending a game at the stadium
Here's a gourmet meal at the stadium!
Wow!
Looks so delicious!
Smells so good!
Amazing!
I'm getting hungry!
This is...
Ballpark Burger & 9's &9 Burger!
The most popular!
Wow!
Looks delicious!Looks delicious.
Me too.
When we first opened.
I told you...
The volume is huge!
What?
I want some!
Even the official website says that if you're in doubt, this is the place to go, so I'm sure it's good.
Wow!
Delicious!
Amazing!
And here's the mango & annin pudding in the back.
Mango & Annin Pudding!
This is also one of the basestaff's favorites, so you can't go wrong with it!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
I've never had this before, so I'm curious about it.
Okay, then, let's get started!
Bye bye!
Bon appétit!
Bye-bye!
Let's try it.
Wow! Delicious!
It looks like a face.
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
Can I eat it?
It's so good!
Can you eat it?
With tomatoes and bacon.
And cheese.
That's what makes it so good!
You should try it too!
Okay, now I would like to try the Mango Annin Pudding!Yes, now I would like to continue with the Mango Annin Pudding!
Wow! Wow!
Look!
The pink of the pink.
The rainbow!
It's so summery!
Bon appétit!
Is it melting?
I can't get in!
The Annin is so good!
And lots of mango!
That's why I want to do it this way!
I want some chocolate!
I want some!
Yes!
Thank you.
Bon appétit.
Oh, no.
The spoon is sinking.
Bon appétit.
What do you think?
I see what you mean.
Good, good, good.
That's great!
I want you all to come to this side of the world.
Yes!
The five of us enjoyed Choco's recommendation of spherical gourmet food.
The time is 5:50 p.m.
It's finally time to play ball!
So this time, we were going to learn more about the BayStars and how to get to the Yokohama studio to watch a baseball game.
We were going to learn more about the BayStars and how to go to a baseball game.
How was it, Mirutan?
Well, we really enjoyed wearing BayStars' cheering goods.
We all wore BayStars' cheering goods.
I learned a lot and I'm really looking forward to it!I've already learned a lot and I'm really looking forward to it!
I want to know more about it.
I want to know more about it, and I want to support it so much because of the actual infection.
And you, Choco.
Thank you very much.
I had fun, too.
Thank you.
I'm glad you guys came in your uniforms.
I hope we can get infected together.
So after this, I'm going to close the video.
I'd like to close the video and let you finish the game.
Choco had to leave here because of his next job.
I wanted to watch the game with you.
I'll see you next time.
I'll be there.
Cheer for me!
Please do!
So, these four of us will be cheering for you.
See you again in the next video!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
There's someone I'd like to say hello to.
Can I have a minute?
Yes!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, my God!
Hey, guys.
Wow.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
So, what do you want me to do?
You get used to it?
Wow! That's great!
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Cute.
Amazing. I got to be good friends with Kirara.
The glitter duo.
I like glitter. Kira Kira duo.